Strike Files of the U.S. Department of Justice, Pt. 1 on Microfilm 5897 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Casefile 16-82 through 16-116 (Reel 8)
  - [Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Company Strike, West Allis, Wisconsin] Casefile 16-85-1, 1941; 4 (Reel 8)
    March 13-June 28, 1941. 98pp. Subjects: J. Edgar Hoover FBI memoranda concerning investigation of UAW and CIO union organization, strike plans, and Communist influence; investigation of fraud in NLB elections; alleged Communist activities of Harold Christoffel. Emil Costello, and others; American Peace Mobilization. Begins at 0096
  - [Hardin County, Texas, Oil Workers Strike] Casefile 16-87, 1917-1918; 5 (Reel 8)
    October 27, 1917 - April 3, 1918. 44pp. Subjects: Use of federal troops guarding oil fields; IWW Oil Workers Industrial Union organization and strikes; DOJ investigation of IWW activities; U.S. Department of Labor efforts to avert wartime strikes.
  - [Kansas Coal Strike] Casefile 16-94, 1918; 6 (Reel 8)
    January 5-16, 1918. 10pp. Subjects: UMWA strike; Southwestern Interstate Coal Operators Association contract negotiations with Alexander Howatt; efforts to avert wartime strikes. Begins 0238.
  - [Denver, Colorado, Machinists Strike] Casefile 16-99, 1918; 7 (Reel 8)
    March 15-20, 1918. 5pp. Subjects: DOJ deferral of authority in strike of machinists in plants with government contracts; mediation of labor disputes. Begins 0248.
  - [Tampa, Florida, Cigar Factories] Casefile 16-101, 1918; 8 (Reel 8)
    May 6-13, 1918. 11pp. Subjects: AFL Cigarmakers strike; Samuel Gompers' request for DOJ investigation of manufacturers' association. Begins 0253.
  - [Wagner Electric Manufacturing Company Strike] Casefile 16-105, 1918; 9 (Reel 8)
    June 4 - October 7, 1918. 41pp. Subjects: International Association of Machinist strike in St. Louis, Missouri; DOJ policy concerning the use of injunctions in labor disputes; U.S. Marshal deployment of deputies enforcing temporary injunction against strikes; wartime efforts to avert labor disputes. Begins 0264.
  - [Thayer, Illinois, Coal Miners Strike] Casefile 16-106, 1918; 10 (Reel 8)
    June 20-29, 1918. 5pp. Subjects: UMWA efforts to avert local wartime strikes. Begins 0305.
  - [Pacific Electric Railway Strike] Casefile 16-108, 1918; 11 (Reel 8)
    July 2-22, 1918. 10pp. Subjects: DOJ intervention in strike against railway serving San Pedro, California, submarine base; use of injunctions in wartime labor disputes. Begins 0310.
  - [Neville Island, Pennsylvania, Ordnance Plant] Casefile 16-110, 1918; 12 (Reel 8)
    October 3-7, 1918. 6pp. Subjects: U.S. Attorney report on labor unrest in the Pittsburgh region. DOJ referral of cases to the National War Labor Board; wartime efforts to avert labor dispute involving carpenters' union. Begins 0320.
  - [Minneapolis-St. Paul, Minnesota, Telephone Workers Strike] Casefile 16-111, 1918-1920; 13 (Reel 8)
    November 15, 1918-April 29, 1920. 57pp. Subjects: DOJ policy concerning U.S. Attorney payment of bail bonds for alleged violators of injunction; U.S. Post Office Department request for DOJ prosecution of strikers; use of injunctions in labor disputes; mob violence and intimidation; employment of strikebreakers in telephone system operating under federal control. Begins at 0326.
  - [South Atlantic Telephone & Telegraph Company Strike] Casefile 16-112, 1918; 14 (Reel 8)
    November 26-December 19, 1918. 34pp. Subjects: U.S. Post Office Department request for DOJ prosecution of strikers at Miami, Florida; affidavits concerning alleged interference by strikers with operations of the company. Begins 0383.
  - [Palestine, Texas, Telephone Workers Strike] Casefile 16-113, 1918; 15 (Reel 8)
    November 29-December 26, 1918. 28pp. Subjects: Samuel Gompers' request for DOJ investigation of local situation; strike involving local union of the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers; mediation and use of injunctions in labor disputes; contract negotiations concerning "closed shop" issues and wages; U.S. Post Office Department investigation of case and request for DOJ prosecution of strikers. Begins at 0417.
  - [Kansas City Street Car Strike] Casefile 16-144. Section 1, 1918-1919; 16 (Reel 8)
    December 30, 1918-October 22, 1919. 198pp. Subjects: U.S. Marshal deployment of deputies guarding property of the Kansas City Railways Company; investigation of strike by special assistant to the attorney general; use of injunction of strike by special assistant to the attorney general; use of injunctions in labor disputes; Amalgamated Association of Street and Electric Railway Employees; Kansas City, Kansas, Chamber of Commerce intervention in case. Begins a 0455.
  - Casefile 16-14. Section 2, 1919-1920; 17 (Reel 8)
    November 5, 1919-November 4, 1920. 48pp. Subjects: DOJ dismissal after continuance of conspiracy charges against strikers; DOJ communications with defense attorneys and Samuel Gompers concerning case; U.S. Marshal request for reimbursement of Kansas City Railway Company for funds advanced to deputies guarding their property. Begins at 0643.
  - Casefile 16-114. Section 3, 1918-1920; 18 (Reel 8)
    October 13, 1918-Octobers 26, 1920. 96pp. Subjects: Investigation of strike by special assistant to the attorney general; U.S. Marshal employment of special deputies; use of injunctions in labor disputes. Begins at 0691.
  - [Illinois Central Railroad and Yazoo and Mississippi Valley Railroad Strike in Memphis, Tennessee] Casefile 16-115, 1919; 19 (Reel 8)
    January 12-27, 1919. 19pp. Subject: Strike by white switchmen against employment of blacks on crews. Begins at 0787.
  - [New York Harbor Tugboat Strike] Casefile 16-116, 1919; 20 (Reel 8)
    January 11-March 31, 1919. 25pp. Subjects: U.S. Fuel Administration opinion concerning wartime need to facilitate shipment of coal; DOJ interpretation of Clayton Act protection of labor right to strike. Begins at 0796.
- Casefile 16-121 through 16-130 (Reel 9)
  - [Argo, Illinois, Corn Products Refining Company Strike] Casefile 16-121, 1919; 1 (Reel 9)
    July 14-18, 1919. 5pp. Subjects: Affidavit concerning violence and intimidation exercised by company guards during strike; DOJ deferral of authority to state officials. Begins at 0000.
  - [Toledo, Ohio, Willys-Overland Automobile Workers Strike] Casefile 16-122, 1919; 2 (Reel 9)
    June 3-November 11, 1919. 170pp. Subjects: Appointment of special attorney to monitor enforcement of restraining order issued by U.S. District Court Judge John M. Killets; use of injunctions in labor disputes; contempt of court proceedings against local union leadership; International Association of Machinists; Automobile District Council; mob violence and intimidation; allegations of IWW influence in strike; DOJ suppression of radical publications; DOJ policy for concerning appointment of special deputies in civil lawsuits. Begins at 0005.
  - [Polk County, Florida, Phosphate Mines Strike] Casefile 16-125-19, 1919-1920; 3 (Reel 9)
    July 5, 1919-Jul 16, 1920. 56pp. Subjects: Employment of black strikebreakers by employers; eviction of strikers from company housing; U.S. Marshal deployment of special deputies guarding trains running in phosphate district. Begins at 0175.
  - [Atlanta, Georgia, Western Union Telegraph Company Strike] Casefile 16-125-19, 1919; 4 (Reel 9)
    June 6-October 4, 1919. 120pp. Subjects: Alleged improper use of federal troops guarding strikebreakers; requests for DOJ involvement in case; U.S. Post Office Department operation of telegraph and telephone lines; mob violence and intimidation; American Bar Association interest in the case. Begins at 0231.
  - [New Albany, Indiana, Telephone Strike] Casefile 16-125-26, 1919; 5 (Reel 9)
    July 10-23, 1919. 20pp. Subjects: U.S. Post Office Department operation of telegraph and telephone lines; allegations of mob violence and intimidation. Begins at 0351.
  - [Louisville, Kentucky, Telephone Strike] Casefile 16-125-30, 1919; 6 (Reel 9)
    July 7-23, 1919. 30pp. Subjects: U.S> Post Office Department operation of telegraph and telephone lines; allegations of mob violence and intimidation. Begins at 0371.
  - [New Orleans, Louisiana, Western Union Telegraph Company Strike] Casefile 16-125-32, 1919; 7 (Reel 9)
    June 9-July 23, 1919. 20pp. Subjects: U.S. Post Office Department operation of telephone and telegraph likes; allegations of mob violence and intimidation. Begins at 0401.
  - [St. Louis, Missouri, Telephone Strike] Casefile 16-125-42, 1919; 8 (Reel 9)
    June 27-July 23, 1919. 30pp. Subjects: U.S. Post Office Department operation of telephone and telegraph likes; allegations of mob violence and intimidation. Begins at 0421.
  - [Reno, Nevada, Telephone Strike] Casefile 16-125-46, 1919; 9 (Reel 9)
    July2-23, 1919. 35pp. Subjects: U.S. Post Office Department operation of telephone and telegraph likes; allegations of mob violence and intimidation; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers contract negotiations. Begins at 0451.
  - [Cleveland, Ohio, Telephone Strike] Casefile 16-125-57, 1919-1921; 10 (Reel 9)
    July 15, 1919-June 16 1921. 60pp. Subjects: U.S. Post Office Department operation of telephone and telegraph likes; allegations of mob violence and intimidation; indictment, trial, and appeal of strikers on conspiracy charges. Begins at 0486.
  - [Youngstown, Ohio, Telephone Strike] Casefile 16-125-58, 1919; 11 (Reel 9)
    Jul 18-25, 1919. 14pp. Subjects: Mob violence and intimidation; U.S. Post Office Department operation of telephone and telegraph lines; Central Union Telephone Company employment of strikebreakers and armed guards; community support for strikers. Begins at 0546.
  - Casefile 16-125-58. Previously Restricted Materials, 1919; 12 (Reel 9)
    July 19-21, 1919. 8pp. Subjects: Bureau of Investigation surveillance of strikers and interviews with local officials and residents. Begins at 0560.
  - [Oklahoma City Telephone Strike] Casefile 16-125-59, 1919-1920; 13 (Reel 9)
    June 19, 1919-January 30, 1920. 229pp. Subjects: Indictment of strikers and their attorney for conspiracy to interfere with operations of Western Union Telegraph Company; U.S. Post Office Department operations of telephone and telegraph lines; Commercial Telegraphers Union; mob violence and intimidation; protests against alleged antilabor bias of U.S. Attorney for the Western District of Oklahoma; DOJ efforts to find work for paroled German seamen in Oklahoma. Begins at 0568.
  - Casefile 16-125-59. Previously Restricted Materials, 1919; 14 (Reel 9)
    June 28, July 1, 1919. 9pp. Subjects: Indictment of strikers and their attorney for conspiracy to interfere with operations of Western Union Telegraph Company; use of injunctions in labor disputes; mob violence and intimidation. Begins at 0797.
  - [Superior, Wisconsin, Great Northern Ore Docks Strike] Casefile 16-126, 1918; 15 (Reel 9)
    June 28-August 2, 1918. 11pp. Subjects: DOJ cooperation with U.S. Department of Labor in wartime arbitration of labor disputes; Finnish immigrants; alleged IWW involvement. Begins at 0806.
  - [Tonopah, Nevada, Miners Strike] Casefile 16-129, 1919; 16 (Reel 9)
    August 25-27, 1919. 4pp. Subjects: U.S. Attorney request for appointment of deputy U.S. Marshals; general strike; alleged IWW involvement. Begins at 0817.
  - [Bituminous Coal Strike] Casefile 16-130, 1919; 17 (Reel 9)
    Subfile 0. October 30-December 16, 1919. 310pp. Subjects: Personal correspondence to Attorney General A. Mitchell Palmer commending him on his stand in the coal strike situation, J-Z; use of injunctions in labor disputes; federal prosecution of strikebreakers; UMWA. Begins at 0821.
- Casefile 16-130. Continued (Reel 10)
  - [Bituminous Coal Strike] Casefile 16-130 cont, 1919; 1 (Reel 10)
    Subfile 0. October 30-December 22, 1919. Subjects: Personal correspondence to Attorney General A. Mitchell Palmer commending him on his stand in the coal strike situation, A-H; use of injunctions in labor disputes; federal protection of strikebreakers. Begins at 0000.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfield 2 [Subfield 0, Section 3], 1919; 2 (Reel 10)
    November 6-7, 1920. 6pp. Subject: Answers to circular no, 1006 concerning U.S. v. Frank J. Hayes, et. al. Begins at 0288.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 2 [Subfile 0, Section 3], 1920; 3 (Reel 10)
    February 9, 1920. 2pp. Subject: Answer to circular no. 1021. Begins at 0294.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 4 [Subfile 0, Section 4], 1919-1920; 4 (Reel 10)
    October 31, 1919-March 6, 1920. 193pp. Subjects: U.S. Fuel Administration; U.S. Railroad Administration; regulation of coal prices; investigation of alleged profiteering in the coal trade. Begins at 0294
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 1, Section 1. Alabama, 1919; 5 (Reel 10)
    October 28-November 29, 1919. 162pp. Subjects: UMWA contract negotiations in Alabama; correspondence with coal operators regarding evictions of striking miners and refusal to reemploy alleged agitators; UMWA District 20; Southern Afro-American Federation of Industrial Brotherhood; violence and intimidation directed against black coal miners; affidavits of UMWA strikes regarding coal operators' refusal to rehire them. Begins at 0489.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 1, Section 2. Alabama, 1919-1921; 6 (Reel 10)
    December 1, 1919-January 6, 1921. 187pp. Subjects: Violence and intimidation directed against black coal miners; UMWA and AFL officials correspondence regarding state militia actions in Alabama coal mining district; open shop versus closed shop issues; mediation of labor dispute; Southern Afro-American Federation of Industrial Brotherhood; U.S. Marshal deployment of special deputies guarding coal mines. Begins at 0651.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 4. Alaska Territory, 1919; 7 (Reel 10)
    December 11, 1919. 2pp. Subject: Suggestion to release coal reserves held in Alaska to break coal strike. Begins at 0838.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 9. Arkansas, 1919-1920; 8 (Reel 10)
    November 29, 1919-February 19, 1920. 50pp. Subjects: Arkansas coal strike; UMWA contract negotiations. Begins at 0840.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 11. California, 1919; 9 (Reel 10)
    November 7-Decembe 26, 1919. 23pp. Subjects: Citizen disapproval of action of the Board of Supervisors of San Francisco, California, criticizing the ole of the federal government in this coal strike; regulation of coal prices. Begins at 890.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 13. Colorado, 1919-1922; 10 (Reel 10)
    November 5, 1919-February 22, 1922. 171pp. Subjects: Miner protests against actions of the State Industrial Commission of Colorado U.S. senator's request for DOJ investigation of alleged seditious correspondence from UMWA local union protesting the Sterling-Graham Peace Time Sedition Bill; regulation of coal prices; DOJ prosecution of the coal operations for alleged violations of the Leve Act; coal company protests against wage increases; mediation and the use of injunctions in labor disputes UMWA District 15 contract negotiations; allegations of IWW involvement in strike; UMWA protest against implementation of the Rockefeller Industrial Plan at the Colorado Fuel and Iron Company; Bureau of Investigation report regarding John. L. Lewis, Frank Farringdon, and William Z. Foster; UMWA factionalism and internal politics. Begins at 0913
- Casefile 16-130. Continued (Reel 11)
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 14. Connecticut, 1919-1920; 1 (Reel 11)
    November 17, 1919-Febuary 9, 1920. 20pp. Subjects: Regulation of coal prices; U.S. Fuel Administration. Begins at 0000.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 15. Delaware, 1920; 2 (Reel 11)
    January 27-February 7, 1920. 6pp. Subjects: Regulation of coal prices; U.S. Fuel Administration. Begins at 0020.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 16. District of Columbia, 1919-1920; 3 (Reel 11)
    November 4, 1919-May 7, 1920. 14pp. Subject: Regulation of coal prices; U.S. Fuel Administration; arbitration and use of injunctions of labor disputes. Begins at 0026.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 19. Georgia, 1919-1920; 4 (Reel 11)
    November 3, 1919-Mach 16, 1920. 7pp. Subjects: Regulation of coal prices; U.S. Fuel Administration; use of injunctions in labor disputes. Begins at 0040.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 22. Idaho, 1919; 5 (Reel 11)
    November 15, 1919. 2pp. Subjects: Regulation of coal prices; U.S. Fuel Administration. Begins at 0047.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 23. Illinois, 1919-1920; 6 (Reel 11)
    October 31, 1919-July 30, 1920. 228pp. Subjects: Regulation of coal prices; arbitration of labor disputes; UMWA District 12 contact negotiations with Bituminous Coal Operators Association of Illinois; DOJ antitrust investigation of coal operators; U.S. Fuel Administration; Peabody Coal Company plan of importing labor from Alabama to work in Harlan County, Kentucky; worker complaints regarding interest charges on purchase from company stores in Pinckneyville, Illinois; UMWA District 12 president Frank Farringdon circulars during World War I; UMWA factionalism and internal politics; open shop versus closed shop and check off system issues; arrest of Frank Farrington for violating injunction; employer complaints concerning effects of coal strike; steel workers union request for federal arbitration of steel strike. Begins at 0049.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 27. Iowa, 1919-1920; 7 (Reel 11)
    November 19, 1919- September 11, 1920. 61pp. Subjects: UMWA District 13 negotiations with Iowa Coal Operators Association; regulation of coal prices; U.S. Fuel Administration; U.S. Railroad Administration; proposal by governor of Iowa for state operation of coal mines. Begins at 0277.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 29. Kansas, 1919-1922; 8 (Reel 11)
    November 4, 1919-January 9, 1922. 199pp. Subjects: Alleged lawlessness and radicalism among Italian immigrants; UMWA strike benefits; regulation of coal prices; U.S. Fuel Administration; U.S. Railroad Administration; proposal by governor of Kansas for state operation of coal mines; UMA District 14 resolution in support of IWW; IWW General Defense Committee circular by William D. Haywood; statistics regarding strikes in UMWA District 14 during World War I; arrest of UMWA District 14 president Alexander Howat for violating injunction; mediation of labor disputes; UMWA District 14 negotiations with Southwestern Interstate Coal Operations Association; John L. Lewis telegrams; National Coal Association; local union support for strike. Begins at 0338.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 30. Kentucky, 1919-1921; 9 (Reel 11)
    November 5, 1919-March 1, 1921. 209pp. Subjects: Local union complaint regarding mine closure; regulation of coal prices; use of injunctions in labor disputes; U.S. Fuel Administration; Fair Price Commission; U.S. Railroad Administration; closed shop versus open shop issues; arbitration of labor disputes; violence and intimidation; blacklisting of UMWA members by mine operators; UMWA strike benefits; strike beakers. Begins at 0527.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 32. Louisiana, 1919-1920; 10 (Reel 11)
    November 4, 1919-Febuaru 24, 1920. 4pp. Subjects: Regulation of coal prices; U.S. Fuel Administration; use of injunctions in labor disputes. Begins at 0736.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 35. Maryland, 1919-1921; 11 (Reel 11)
    November 19, 1919-August 25, 1921. 161pp. Subjects: Blacklisting of UMWA members by mine operators; arbitration of labor disputes; UMWA District 16 contact negotiations; regulations of coal prices. Begins at 0740.
- Casefile 16-130. Continued (Reel 12)
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 36. Massachusetts, 1919-1920; 1 (Reel 12)
    November 12, 1919-March 19, 1920. 13pp. Subjects: Regulation of coal prices; U.S Fuel Administration; blacklisting of UMWA members in Maryland; local union support for railroad strike. Begins at 0000.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 37. Michigan, 1919-1920; 2 (Reel 12)
    November 4, 1919-May 8, 1920. 44pp. [no file folder] Subjects: Regulation of coal prices; U.S. Fuel Administration; arbitration of labor disputes. Begins at 0013.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 39. Minnesota, 1919-1920; 3 (Reel 12)
    October 31, 1919-March 4, 1920. 9pp. Subjects: Regulation of coal prices; U.S. Fuel Administration; use of injunctions in labor disputes; proposal by governor of North Dakota for state operation of mines; citizen protest against strike plans. Begins at 0057.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 40. Mississippi, 1919; 4 (Reel 12)
    December 1-13, 1919. 5pp. [frames 0066 and 0069 repeated]. Begins at 0066.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 42. Missouri, 1919-1922; 5 (Reel 12)
    November 28, 1919-January 24, 1922. 177pp. Subjects: Indictment and prosecution of James Cannon and Charles Baker of Lever Act violations for encourages UMWA wok stoppage; regulation of coal prices; U.S. Fuel Administration; Bureau of Investigation attempted surveillance of local union telegraph messages in Kansas; John L. Lewis letter regarding mediation of UMWA District 25 labor dispute in Missouri; local union work stoppage after Southwestern Interstate Coal Operators Association refusal to pay wage increase mandated in strike settlement; UMWA District 25 contact negotiations; UMWA strike benefits; use of injunctions in labor disputes; antirust suit against UMWA strike benefits; use of injunctions in labor disputes; antitrust suit against UMWA stemming from 1914 strike at Bache-Denman Coal Company in Arkansas. Begins at 0069.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 44. Montana, 1919-1920; 6 (Reel 12)
    November 1, 1919-January 12, 1920. 63pp.[frame 0246 repeated]. Subjects: Regulations of coal prices; U.S. Fuel Administration; local union protest of coal operators association refusal to pay wage increase mandated in strike settlement; U.S. railroad Administration; governor or Montana support for continued operation of mines by volunteer workers under protection of federal troops; deportation proceedings against radical immigrant labor; use of injunctions in labor disputes; UMWA strike benefits. Begins at 0246.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 45. Nebraska, 1919-1920; 7 (Reel 12)
    December 4, 1919-Januay 27, 1920. 11pp. [frames 0308 and 0317 repeated] Subjects: Regulation of coal prices; alleged profiteering by coal dealers; U.S. Fuel Administration. Begins at 0308.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 48. New Jersey, 1919-1920; 8 (Reel 12)
    November 1, 1919-January 27, 1920. 21pp. Subjects: Regulation of coal prices; U.S. Railroad Administration; U.S. Fuel Administration. Begins at 0317.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 49. New Mexico, 1919-1920; 9 (Reel 12)
    November 20, 1919-December 15, 1919. 10pp. [frames 0338 and 046 repeated]. Subjects: Governor of New Mexico support for continued employment of strikebreakers following setlement of stike; posecution of agitators under Lever Act; refusal by coal operators to re-employ UMWA members. Begins at 0338.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 50. New York, 1919-1920; 10 (Reel 12)
    November 3, 1919-March 27, 1920. 59pp. Subjects: Regulation of coal prices; U.S. Railroad Administration; U.S. Fuel Administration. Begins at 0346.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 54. North Carolina, 1919-1920; 11 (Reel 12)
    November 10, 1919-February 10, 1920. 27pp. [frame 0406 and 0431 repeated] Subjects: Regulation of coal prices; U.S. Fuel Administration. Begins at 0406.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 56. North Dakota, 1919-1920; 12 (Reel 12)
    November 16, 1919-July 17, 1922. 61pp. Subjects: U.S. District Judge Charles F. Amidon opinion in civil suit against the governor of North Dakota for implementing state operations of coal mines; UMWA District 27 contract negotiations; U.S. Railroad Administration; U.S Fuel Administration. Begins a 0431.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 57. Ohio (Southern District), 1919-1920; 13 (Reel 12)